

CONTACT



+375(44)511-11-79



vitaliybyaniskov@gmail.com



https://github.com/AniskovVitaliy

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021

Gomel State University name after F.Skorina Software developer

SKILLS

PHP (Opencart, Laravel, 1C Bitrix)

JS, JQUERY

Redis

MySQL

Docker

CSS, SCSS

HTML

GIT

LANGUAGES

English (A2)

Russian (Native)

Vitaliy Aniskov

PHP developer

ABOUT ME

I'm a developer with over two years of experience in commercial development. In general I work as full stack developer:

Backend: native php, opencart, bitrix (a little), laravel (a little).

Frontend: Js, Jquery, CSS, HTML, SCSS.

I'm constantly developing and striving for high-quality, extensible and understandable code.

WORK EXPERIENCE

KSK. Homel. Belarus

01.03.2022 - until today

Software developer

Development and support web site https://ksk.by

Technologies:

- PHP, Opencart and Laravel (a little)
- JS, JQUERY, HTML, CSS
- Codeception (test), Xdebug, xprof
- PHPstorm, Navicat, Insomnia, GIT

Responsibilities:

- Development of modules and libraries in Opencart
- Developer of frontend using JS, JQUERY, CSS
- Development of parser using PHPQuery
- Development of tests using the Codeception framework
- Profiling using xprof
- Writing SQL query

Media Line Group. Homel. Belarus

01.11.2021 - 01.03.2022

Software developer

Outsourcing, development and technical support of websites on 1C Bitrix.

Technologies:

- 1C-Bitrix, PHP
- JS, JQUERY, HTML, CSS
- Rest Api

Responsibilities:

- Development components using 1C-Bitrix.
- Development of parser for unloading goods from docx, xml, csv, as well as web sites.
- Working with different APIs: google tag manager, google map, google analytic.
- Administration 1C-Bitrix.

Homselmash. Homel. Belarusian

2011 - 2020

- Foreman
- Programmable machine operation "MAZAK QTN 250"

Foreman (2019-2020) - Work with documents, production control, production process management, etc. Programmable machine operation (2011-2019) - Setting up a machining turning center to produce the necessary parts. Control of manufactured parts.